Plain text is great but it's still
纯文本很好 但仍然是
human language with all its variations and bells and whistles.
含有变形和修饰的人类语言
Next, we'll try to reduce some of that complexity.
接下来 我们将尝试降低它的复杂度
In the English language,
在英语语言中
the starting letter of the first word in any sentence is usually capitalized.
所有句子第一个词的首字母一般是大写
All caps are sometimes used for emphasis and for stylistic reasons.
有时全部字母大写 用于表示强调和区分风格
While this is convenient for
这对人类读者而言非常方便
a human reader from the standpoint of a machine learning algorithm,
但从机器学习算法的角度来说
it does not make sense to differentiate between Car,
区分 Car，car 和 CAR 没有意义
car, and CAR, they all mean the same thing.
它们都是一个意思
Therefore, we usually convert every letter in our text to a common case,
因此我们一般会把文本中的所有字母统一转换成大写/小写
usually lowercase, so that each word is represented by a unique token.
一般是小写 这样每个词都能用唯一的词条 (token) 表示
Here's some sample text,
这是文本样本
a review for the movie, The Second Renaissance,
是电影《机器的复兴》的一段影评
a story about intelligent robots that get into a fight with humans over their rights.
这部电影是关于智能机器人与人类作斗争 来争取权利的故事
Yup, the way we treat robots these days.
我们现在就是这样对待机器人的
Anyway, if we have the reviews stored in a variable called text,
总之 如果将影评存储在名为 text 的变量中
converting it to lowercase is a simple call to the lore method in Python.
将其转换成小写 只需在 Python 中调用 lower 方法即可
Here's what it looks like after a conversion.
这是转换之后的样子
Note all the letters that were changed.
请注意所有更改后的字母
Other languages may or may not have a case
其它语言可能有 也可能没有对应的大小写
equivalent but similar principles may apply depending on your NLP task,
但是根据你的 NLP 任务的不同 类似原理可能也适用
you may want to remove special characters like periods, question marks,
你可能想清除文本中的句号 问号 感叹号等
and exclamation points from the text and only
特殊字符 仅保留
keep letters of the alphabet and maybe numbers.
字母表中的字母和数字
This is especially useful when we are looking
在底层细节不太重要的
at text documents as a whole in applications
文档分类和聚类等应用中
like document classification and
将所有文本文档作为一个整体
clustering where the low level details do not matter a lot.
这个方法特别有效
Here, we can use a regular expression that matches
这里可以使用正则表达式
everything that is not a lowercase A to Z,
匹配那些不是大小写 A 至 Z 的字母
or digits zero to nine,
或者数字 0 到 9 的范围之外的所有字符
and replaces them with a space.
并用空格代替
This approach avoids having to specify all punctuation characters,
这个方法无需指定所有标点符号
but you can use other regular expressions as well.
但是也可以采用其它正则表达式
Lowercase conversion and punctuation removal
进行大小写转换和标点删除
are the two most common text normalization steps.
是两个最常见的文本标准化步骤
Whether you need to apply them and at what stage
是否需要 以及在哪个阶段使用这两个步骤
depends on your end goal and the way you design your pipeline.
取决于你的最终目标和管道的设计